{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"evacuating the bystanders.",
					"calling the hazardous materials team.",
					"ensuring your personal safety.",
					"identifying the hazardous material."
				],
				"question": "The most important consideration at the scene of a hazardous materials incident is:",
				"source": "See Scene Safety"
			},
			"back": "ensuring your personal safety."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"stares at certain parts of another person’s anatomy.",
					"requests sexual favors in exchange for something else.",
					"makes rude remarks about a person’s body parts.",
					"touches another person without his or her consent."
				],
				"question": "Quid pro quo, a type of sexual harassment, occurs when the harasser:",
				"source": "See Workplace Issues"
			},
			"back": "requests sexual favors in exchange for something else."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"increased self-image from performing well under a challenging situation.",
					"the inability to remain focused, because the task at hand is demanding.",
					"short term loss of energy due to the high physical demands of the job.",
					"long-term feelings of being overwhelmed by the nature of the call."
				],
				"question": "Characteristics of eustress following dispatch to a high-speed motor vehicle collision may include:",
				"source": "See General Health, Wellness, and Resilience"
			},
			"back": "increased self-image from performing well under a challenging situation."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"excessive blood splashing or splattering.",
					"careless handling of sharps.",
					"noncompliance with standard precautions.",
					"lack of proper immunizations."
				],
				"question": "The spread of HIV and hepatitis in the healthcare setting can usually be traced to:",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "careless handling of sharps."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"use a bleach and water solution at a 1:2 dilution ratio to thoroughly wipe all surfaces.",
					"clean all surfaces and patient contact areas with a mixture of alcohol and water.",
					"allow surfaces to air dry unless otherwise indicated in the product directions.",
					"spray the contaminated areas and then immediately wipe them dry with a towel."
				],
				"question": "When decontaminating the back of your ambulance after a call, you should:",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "allow surfaces to air dry unless otherwise indicated in the product directions."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"have been infected with hepatitis A in the past.",
					"have a weak immune system.",
					"received a hepatitis B vaccination.",
					"are older than 35 years of age."
				],
				"question": "Vaccination against the hepatitis A virus is unnecessary if you:",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "have been infected with hepatitis A in the past."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"the TB disease is currently dormant but might later become active.",
					"you are actively infected with TB.",
					"you have been exposed to TB.",
					"you have never been exposed to TB."
				],
				"question": "A positive TB skin test indicates that:",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "you have been exposed to TB."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Ensure the vehicle is stable.",
					"Request another ambulance.",
					"Check for other patients.",
					"Contact medical control."
				],
				"question": "What should you do before attempting to access a patient trapped in a vehicle?",
				"source": "See Scene Safety"
			},
			"back": "Ensure the vehicle is stable."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Age",
					"Gender",
					"Immunity",
					"Race"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following is the most significant factor in determining whether a person will become ill from certain germs?",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "Immunity"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"tension among coworkers and supervisors.",
					"punitive action and the loss of a job.",
					"substandard or inappropriate patient care.",
					"low morale and frequently missed shifts."
				],
				"question": "The most serious consequence of drug or alcohol abuse among EMS personnel is:",
				"source": "See Workplace Issues"
			},
			"back": "substandard or inappropriate patient care."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"distress.",
					"wellness.",
					"eustress.",
					"resilience."
				],
				"question": "The capacity of an individual to cope with and recover from stress is called:",
				"source": "See Caring for Critically Ill and Injured Patients"
			},
			"back": "resilience."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"24",
					"12",
					"72",
					"six"
				],
				"question": "A critical incident stress debriefing should be conducted no longer than ________ hours following the incident.",
				"source": "See Stress Management on the Job"
			},
			"back": "72"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"providing large amounts of caffeine to the rescue workers.",
					"requesting a CISM team to provide on-scene peer support.",
					"conducting a critical incident stress debriefing the next day.",
					"allowing each worker to sleep in 15- to 30-minute increments."
				],
				"question": "You have been working at the scene of a major building collapse for eight hours. Many injured people are still being removed, and everyone is becoming frustrated and losing focus. This situation is most effectively managed by:",
				"source": "See Stress Management on the Job"
			},
			"back": "requesting a CISM team to provide on-scene peer support."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"direct contact.",
					"animals or insects.",
					"smoke or dust.",
					"inanimate objects."
				],
				"question": "Vectorborne transmission of an infectious organism occurs via:",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "animals or insects."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"smoke and toxic gases.",
					"carbon dioxide deficiency.",
					"risk of building collapse.",
					"high ambient temperatures."
				],
				"question": "Hazards that are associated with a structural fire include all of the following, except:",
				"source": "See Scene Safety"
			},
			"back": "carbon dioxide deficiency."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"are not secured with a strap.",
					"offer little or no side protection.",
					"do not have shatterproof lenses.",
					"have large, rounded lenses."
				],
				"question": "Prescription glasses do not provide adequate eye protection because they:",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "offer little or no side protection."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Mumps",
					"Rubella",
					"Chickenpox",
					"Syphilis"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following infectious diseases confers no protection from reinfection after exposure?",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "Syphilis"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Alarm response, reaction and resistance, and recovery",
					"Delayed reaction, alarm response, and physical recovery",
					"Immediate reaction, psychological exhaustion, and recovery",
					"Reaction and resistance, euphoria, and physical exhaustion"
				],
				"question": "General adaptation syndrome is characterized by which of the following phases?",
				"source": "See Stress Management on the Job"
			},
			"back": "Alarm response, reaction and resistance, and recovery"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"undergo an annual physical examination.",
					"wash your hands in between patient contacts.",
					"undergo annual testing for tuberculosis and hepatitis.",
					"ensure that your immunizations are up-to-date."
				],
				"question": "The simplest, yet most effective method of preventing the spread of an infectious disease is to:",
				"source": "See Infectious and Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "wash your hands in between patient contacts."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-02-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"wear socks made of heavy-duty cotton.",
					"wear at least three layers of clothing.",
					"avoid outer clothing with zippers.",
					"wear a heavy, thick jacket or coat."
				],
				"question": "The most effective way to preserve your own body heat when functioning in cold, wet weather is to:",
				"source": "See Scene Safety"
			},
			"back": "wear at least three layers of clothing."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-02",
		"label": "Chapter 2"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}